Eloise Hubbard Linscott collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series II: Sound Recordings
  - AFS 06053, November 8, 1941, 1 12-inch disc
    - Side B:, afc1942002_afs6053b
      Performed by Frank Cates, in Rockland, Maine. Collector's original ID: B3.
      - Old Zip Coon
      - Irish Washerwoman
      - Speed the Plough [Speed the Plow]
  - AFS 06054, November 8, 1941, 1 12-inch disc
    Performed by Frank Cates, in Rockland, Maine. Collector's original ID: B4.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_afs6054a
      - Reel
      - Come Haste to the Wedding
      - Old Zip Coon
    - Side B:, afc1942002_afs6054b
      - Clog
      - Devil's Dream
      - Chorus Jig
      - Irish Washerwoman [fragment]
      - Waltz
  - AFS 06055, November 8, 1941, 1 12-inch disc
    - Side A:, afc1942002_afs6055a
      - Soldier's Joy
      - Speed the Plough [Speed the Plow]
      - Hull's Victory
      - Hornpipe
      - Heel and Toe Polka
    - Side B:, afc1942002_afs6055b
      - Portland Fancy
      - College Hornpipe
      - Pop Goes the Weasel
  - AFS 06058, November 9, 1941, 1 12-inch disc (broken)
    Performed by Herbert D. (Bert) Farnham, in Swanville, Maine. Collector's original ID: C3. Although the collector indicates that "Old Zip Coon" was recorded on Side B, that side is blank.
    - Side A: Music for the dance Chickadee Quadrille, afc1942002_afs6058a
      - Abington
      - Chickadee
      - Chickadee
  - AFS 06059, November 12, 1941, 1 12-inch disc (broken)
    Side B includes both Asa Brown and an unidentified female singer, in Carthage, Maine. Collector's original ID: C4.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_afs6059a
      - Glencoe
      - Lovely Flora, Lily of the West
    - Side B:, afc1942002_afs6059b
      - Lovely Flora
      - The Flying Cloud
  - AFS 06060, November 12, 1941, 1 12-inch disc
    "Lumberman's Alphabet" and "Klondike Jail" performed by Alvin Brown. "The Two Orphans" performed by Asa Brown. All songs recorded in Carthage, Maine. Side B is blank. Collector's original ID: C5.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_afs6060a
      - Lumberman's Alphabet
      - The Two Orphans
      - Klondike Jail
  - AFS 06061, 1 12-inch disc (broken)
    Side A: all songs performed by Gene Staples. Side B: Wynifred Staples Smith performed both "Lord Banner" tracks. Gene Staples performed "Dan Weaver"). Disc recorded in Dixfield, Maine. Collector's original ID: D1.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_afs6061a
      - Geranus, My Son (fragment)
      - Explanation of Dan Weaver fragment, plus chorus
      - I'm Monarch of All I Survey
    - Side B:, afc1942002_afs6061b
      - Cutting test
      - Dan Weaver (fragment)
      - Lord Banner (fragment)
      - Lord Banner
  - AFS 06062, November 12, 1941, 1 12-inch disc
    Side A: the first three songs performed by Gene Staples; the fourth song performed by Wynifred Staples Smith. Side B: all songs performed by Gene Staples. Disc recorded in Dixfield, Maine. Collector's original ID: D2.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_afs6062a
      - The Farmer's Boy
      - Uncle Sam's Farm
      - When the Roll Is Called Up Yonder
      - Caroline of Edinboro Town
    - Side B:, afc1942002_afs6062b
      - Lovely Lou
      - Daisy Dean
      - Rena Bell
  - AFS 06063, November 12, 1941, 1 12-inch disc
    Side A: songs 1 through 6 performed by Wynifred Staples Smith; song 6 performed by Gene Staples. Side B: song performed Gene Staples. Disc recorded in Dixfield, Maine. Collector's original ID: D3.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_afs6063a
      - Fair Charlotte
      - Penobscot River Chantey
      - Jean Francois (fragment) [Boney Was a Warrior]
      - Maid of the Mountain Brow (fragment)
      - Sons of Liberty
      - Lord Lovell
    - Side B:, afc1942002_afs6063b
      - Violin story
  - AFS 06064, November 13, 1941, 1 12-inch disc
    Performed by Hiram Virgin, in Mexico, Maine. Side B is blank. See SR308 A for a dubbed version of this recording. Collector's original ID: D4.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_afs6064a
      - Western Ranger
      - George Riley (fragment)
      - The Jam on Gerry's Rocks (fragment)
  - AFS 06065, November 16, 1941, 1 12-inch disc (broken)
    Performed by George (Rocky Mountain George) Brown, in Tamworth, New Hampshire. See SR308 B for a dubbed version of this recording.Collector's original ID: D5.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_afs6065a
      - The Robber Song
    - Side B:, afc1942002_afs6065b
      - My True Love was a Fisherman [John Riley (Bound for America)]
      - My Old New Hampshire Home
  - AFS 06066, November 16, 1941 (Side A); November 9, 1941 (Side B), 1 12-inch disc
    Side A: Performed by George (Rocky Mountain George) Brown, in Tamworth, New Hampshire. Side B: Performed by Mrs. H. Rae Farnham (vocals) and Herbert D. (Bert) Farnham (piano), in Swanville, Maine. Side A was recorded 1941-11-16; Side B was recorded 1941-11-09. Collector's original ID: E1.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_afs6066a
      - Long-Waisted Peggy
      - John Hopper's Hill
      - The Jam on Gerry's Rocks
    - Side B:, afc1942002_afs6066b
      - Peter Emily
      - Some Other Will Do
  - AFS 06067, November 9, 1941, 1 12-inch disc
    Side A: Performed by Betty Gaye Farnham (vocals) and Herbert V. [sic] Farnham (piano). Side B: Performed by Betty Gaye Farnham (vocals and guitar). Disc recorded in Swanville, Maine. Collector's original ID: E2.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_afs6067a
      - Good Morning Jolly Fisherman
      - My Parents Raised Me Tenderly
      - State of Arkansas
    - Side B:, afc1942002_afs6067b
      - The Turkish Shore
      - Frog in the Well
  - AFS 06068, November 9, 1941, 1 12-inch disc
    Side A: Performed by Betty Gaye Farnham (vocals) and Herbert R. (Bert) Farnham (piano). Side B: Performed by Betty Gaye Farnham (vocals and guitar), in Swanville, Maine. "Reuben Haskins" includes yodeling. "High Diddle Daddle" composed by Bert Farnham. Collector's original ID: E3. SR398 may be a copy of this disc.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_afs6068a
      - Old Man Worth
      - High Diddle Daddle
    - Side B:, afc1942002_afs6068b
      - Reuben Haskins
      - Yodeling
  - AFS 06069, November 9, 1941 (Side A and Side B, track 1); November 11, 1941 (Side B, track 2), 1 12-inch disc
    Side A and Side B, track 1, performed by Herbert D. (Bert) Farnham (fiddle), and Mrs. H. Rae Farnham (piano), in Swanville, Maine. Side B, track 2 performed by Charles (Uncle Charlie) Ronco, in Dover-Foxcroft, Maine. Collector's original ID: E4.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_afs6069a
      - Portland Fancy
      - Jane's Hornpipe
      - Jane's Hornpipe
    - Side B:, afc1942002_afs6069b
      - Devil's Dream
      - Rossignol
  - AFS 06070, November 11, 1941, 1 12-inch disc
    Performed by Charles (Uncle Charlie) Ronco, in Dover-Foxcroft, Maine. Collector's original ID: E5.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_afs6070a
      - The Late Evening Dew
    - Side B:, afc1942002_afs6070b
      - The Bachelor's Song
      - Prince Edward Island Song [Peter Emberley]
      - Fair Imogene [Fair Emma Jean]
  - AFS 06071, November 11, 1941 (Side A); November 12, 1941 (Side B), 1 12-inch disc
    Side A: Performed by Charles (Uncle Charlie) Ronco, in Dover-Foxcroft, Maine. Side B: Performed by John Hutchinson, in Berry's Mills, Maine. Collector's original ID: F1.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_afs6071a
      - French Wedding Song
      - Rossignol Sauvage
    - Side B:, afc1942002_afs6071b
      - James Bird
  - AFS 06072, November 11, 1941 (Side A); December 3, 1941 (Side B), 1 12-inch disc
    Side A: Performed by Charles (Uncle Charlie) Ronco, in Dover-Foxcroft, Maine. Side B: Performed by Isaac McNeilly (double harmonica), in Springfield, Massachusetts. Collector's original ID: F2.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_afs6072a
      - The Shanty Boys
    - Side B:, afc1942002_afs6072b
      - The Holyoke Clog
      - The Bowery
      - When Summer Comes Again
      - Devil's Dream
  - AFS 06073, December 3, 1941, 1 12-inch disc
    Performed by Isaac McNeilly (double harmonica and vocals), in Springfield, Massachusetts. Collector's original ID: F3.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_afs6073a
      - Bluebells of Scotland
      - Warsaw (The 42nd Black Watch)
      - Clara Nolan's Ball
    - Side B:, afc1942002_afs6073b
      - Stowaway from Liverpool
      - Grumbling Song
  - AFS 06074, December 3, 1941, 1 12-inch disc
    Performed by Isaac McNeilly (vocals), in Springfield, Massachusetts. Collector's original ID: F4.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_afs6074a
      - Hard Up and Broken Down
      - McCarty's Party
    - Side B:, afc1942002_afs6074b
      - The Moving Job
      - Parody on "Call Me Back Again"
  - AFS 06075, December 3, 1941, 1 12-inch disc
    Performed by Isaac McNeilly (double harmonica and vocals), in Springfield, Massachusetts. Collector's original ID: F5.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_afs6075a
      - The Crooked Bawbee (fragment)
      - Sure I'll Not Go Out with Reilly Any More
      - Little Old Log Cabin in the Lane [two fragments]
    - Side B: Medley, afc1942002_afs6075b
      - Scotch fife tune
      - Wearing o' the Green
      - Untitled
      - Haste to the Wedding [Come Haste to the Wedding]
      - College Hornpipe; White Cockade; Rory O'Moore [The Campbells Are Coming]
  - AFS 06076, December 3, 1941, 1 12-inch disc
    Performed by Isaac McNeilly (flute and vocals), in Springfield, Massachusetts. Side B is blank. Collector's original ID: G1.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_afs6076a
      - On the Warpath
      - I went into a place called a dive [The Bowery]
  - SR001, May 26, 1946, 1 10-inch disc
    Performed by Herbert Meatty (fiddle) and Maynard Meatty (piano), in East Barrington, New Hampshire. Collector's original ID: II.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr001a
      - Lamplighter's Hornpipe
      - Lop-Eared Mule
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr001b
      - Tuning
      - Fisher's Hornpipe
      - The Girl I Left Behind Me
  - SR002, circa 1940-1944, 1 10-inch disc
    Side A: Lena Bourne Fish and William (Bill) Spink; unclear who performed which tune (fiddle playing only). Side B: "Tune the cow died on" performed by Lena Bourne Fish. "Quadrille tunes" and "White Cockade" performed by William (Bill) Spink (fiddle). Recorded in East Jaffrey, New Hampshire. Collecter's original ID: IV.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr002a
      - Beaux of Oak Hill
      - Flowers of Edinburgh
      - Turkey in the Straw
      - The Tempest
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr002b
      - Tune the Cow Died On
      - Quadrille tunes
      - White Cockade
  - SR003, circa 1944, 1 10-inch disc
    Collector's original ID: I.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr003a
      - Untitled
      - Untitled
      - Alouette
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr003b
      - Untitled
      - Turkey in the Straw
      - Devil's Dream
  - SR004, between April and August 1940, 1 10-inch disc
    Performed by Sam Young, Jr., in Laconia, New Hampshire. Includes guitar accompaniment by an unientified person.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr004a
      - Untitled
      - The Jam on Gerry's Rocks
      - Lass of Mohea [Little Mohea]
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr004b
      - Jack Haggerty
  - SR005, circa November 11, 1944, 1 10-inch disc
    Performed by Albert (Al) Quigley, of Nelson, New Hampshire. Collector's original ID: III.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr005a
      - The Rout
      - The Rout (original version by Albert Quigley)
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr005b
      - Soldier's Joy
      - Smash the Windows [Roaring Jelly]
  - SR006, November 7, 1941, 1 10-inch disc
    Performed by Roger Robinson, in Bowdoinham, Maine.
    - Side A: Music for the dance Lady of the Lake, afc1942002_sr006a
      - Old Crane
      - Durang's Hornpipe [Ricketts Hornpipe]
      - Money Musk [Monymusk]
      - Shave and a Haircut
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr006b
      - Hull's Victory
      - When You and I Were Young, Maggie
  - SR007, circa 1940s, 1 10-inch disc
    Performed by the Katahdin Mountaineers.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr007a
      - Haymakers Jig
      - Darktown Strutters Ball
    - Side B: Music for the dance Lady of the Lake, afc1942002_sr007b
      - Over There
      - Keep the Home Fires Burning
      - Smiles
      - Good Morning Mr. Zip-Zip-Zip
      - Just Like The Good Old Colony Times
  - SR008, circa 1940s, 1 10-inch disc
    "Good Old Colony Times" performed by an unidentified woman. "Jolly Old Roger" performed by Eloise Hubbard Linscott (piano and vocals). On Side B, Chet Sargent performed all songs, accompanied by Eloise Hubbard Linscott (on piano). Collector's original ID: IV.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr008a
      - Good Old Colony Times
      - Jolly Old Roger
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr008b
      - Amsterdam [Maid of Amsterdam]
      - Canaday I-O
      - Tittery Nan
  - SR009, circa 1940s, 1 10-inch disc
    Performed by Dick Richardson. Collector's original ID: III.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr009a
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr009b
      - Durang's Hornpipe (with calls)
      - My Love Is But A Lassie
  - SR010, circa 1944, 1 10-inch disc
    Performed by Dick Richardson. Collector's original ID: VI.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr010a
      - Irish Washerwoman
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr010b
      - Twin Sisters
  - SR011, circa 1940s, 1 10-inch disc (broken)
    Performed by Moody [sic]. Collector's original ID: III.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr011a
      - Untitled
      - Flop-Eared Mule
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr011b
      - Devil's Dream
  - SR012, circa 1944, 1 10-inch disc
    Performed by William (Bill) Spink. Although the sleeve notes indicate there are recordings on Side A, it is blank. Collector's original ID: IV.
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr012b
      - Quadrille
  - SR013, circa 1944, 1 10-inch disc
    Side A: Performed by Dick Richardson. Side B: Performed by Albert (Al) Quigley (of Nelson, New Hampshire), Dick Richardson, and Clarice Carr. On all recordings, made in front of an audience, a piano and a fiddle can be heard. Collector's original ID: III.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr013a
      - Red Wing
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr013b
      - Turkey in the Straw
      - Scotch Hornpipe
  - SR014, circa 1944, 1 10-inch disc
    Side A: Performed by Elmer Arno. Side B: Performed by William (Bill) Spink. Collector's original ID: II.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr014a
      - Turkey in the Straw
      - Untitled
      - Untitled
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr014b
      - Turkey in the Straw
      - St. Anne's Reel
  - SR015, circa 1930s, 1 10-inch disc
    Side A: Jennie Jenkins performed by Eloise Hubbard Linscott. Paul Revere's Ride performed by John Hubbard Linscott (the child who can be heard) and his father Charles Hardy Linscott. A-Roving performed on the piano by Eloise Hubbard Linscott. Ferdinand performed by John Hubbard Linscott. Jack Haggerty performed by Eloise Hubbard Linscott. Side B: conservation between Eloise Hubbard Linscott and John Hubbard Linscott, plus a recording of Casey At Bat (original recording on this disc was made at the wrong speed). The documentation for this recording indicates that Willie (Bill) Woodward is also recorded on it. He is associated with the city of Bristol, New Hampshire.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr015a
      - Jennie Jenkins (fragment)
      - Paul Revere's Ride
      - Ferdinand
      - A-Roving
      - Jack Haggerty
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr015b
      - Conversation between Eloise and her son John
      - Casey At Bat
  - SR016, circa April-May 1941, 1 10-inch disc
    Performed by Delude's Orchestra; Pete Miller is the caller on the recording. The location of regular performances is identified in the recording as Miller's Dance Hall, in Manchester, Connecticut.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr016a
      - The Girl I Left Behind Me (with calls)
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr016b
      - Over the Top (tune: Buffalo Gals)
  - SR017, circa 1940, 1 10-inch disc
    Performed by The Singing Smiths. While the caller is not identified here, it is probably R.V. (Raymond) Smith, the caller for the Singing Smiths. Collector's original ID: II.
    - Side A: Music for the dance Haymakers Jig, afc1942002_sr017a
      - Girl I Left Behind Me
      - Darling Nelly Gray [Darling Nellie Gray]
      - Old Zip Coon
      - Golden Slippers
    - Side B: Music for the dance Lady of the Lake, afc1942002_sr017b
      - Soldier's Joy
      - Annie Laurie
      - Going to Boston
  - SR018, October 1940, 1 10-inch disc
    Side A: Performers include George Reed, R.V. (Raymond Ven) Smith, and Ralph C. Merrill. Side B: Performers include The Singing Smiths.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr018a
      - The Sidewalks of New York [chorus only]
      - Canaday I-O
      - Haymakers Jig
      - Darktown Strutters Ball
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr018b
      - I'll Go Riding Down That Texas Trail
      - Cowboy's Sweetheart [fragment]
      - Wild Irish Rose
  - SR019, circa 1940, 1 10-inch disc
    Performers include The Singing Smiths, with R.V. (Raymond) Smith. According to the collector's notes, "Devil's Dream" is performed two and a half times. Side A recorded in an empty dance hall "for orchestra and manager." Side B recorded on the dance floor. Collector's original ID: I.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr019a
      - Green Mountain Volunteers
      - Devil's Dream
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr019b
      - White Cockade (?)
      - Lamplighter's Hornpipe
  - SR020, August 6 or August 10, 1940, 1 10-inch disc
    The male singer on "Mrs. Murphy's Lil Dog" is not identified. All other songs performed by The Singing Smiths. Linscott's note on the disc sleeves suggests that "Mrs. Murphy's Lil Dog" not be played "indisciminately."
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr020a
      - Mrs. Murphy's Lil Dog [Mrs. Murphy's Little Dog]
      - Bird in a Gilded Cage
      - Unidentified waltz
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr020b
      - Old Zip Coon
  - SR021, December 23, 1940, 1 8-inch disc
    Announcements and calls performed by Happy Hale, in Hinsdale, New Hampshire.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr021a
      - Hull's Victory
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr021b
      - Pop Goes the Weasel
  - SR022, circa April-May 1941, 1 10-inch disc
    Performed by Delude's Orchestra. Collector's original ID: I.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr022a
      - Hinkey Dinkey
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr022b
      - Irish Washerwoman
  - SR023, March 15, 1946, 1 10-inch disc
    Disc sleeve notes indicate this disc has "singing ads." Recorded from a radio broadcast on Westinghouse Radio, WBZ (Boston), WBZA (Springfield, Massachusetts). Chet Gaylord performed "I Got A Woman Crazy 'Bout Me" and "I Guess I'm Just A Lucky So and So." Georgia Mae performed "Sioux City Sue" and "Goodbye Lil Darling." Collector's original ID: WB2.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr023a
      - I Got A Woman Crazy 'Bout Me
      - I Guess I'm Just A Lucky So and So
      - Griffin Shoe Polish
      - Chiffon Soap Flakes
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr023b
      - Sioux City Sue
      - Chiquita Bananas (United Fruit Company)
      - Goodbye Lil Darling [Goodbye Little Darling]
  - SR024, March 15, 1946, 1 10-inch disc
    Recorded from a radio broadcast on Westinghouse Radio, WBZ (Boston), WBZA (Springfield, Massachusetts). "Hold On Little Doggies" performed by Georgia Mae. All other tracks are singing advertisements. Collector's original ID: WB2.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr024a
      - Kay Jewelers
      - Hold On Little Doggies
      - Pond's Cream
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr024b
      - Listen and Learn
      - Peabody's
      - REM
      - Duz
      - TEK [sic]
  - SR025, January 8, 1941, 1 10-inch disc
    Recorded from a radio broadcast. Harry S Truman is the speaker. Collector's original ID: I.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr025a
      - State of the Nation
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr025b
      - State of the Nation (continued)
  - SR026, January 20, 1941, 1 10-inch disc
    Recorded from a radio broadcast. Speakers include Franklin D. (Franklin Delano) Roosevelt.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr026a
      - Announcement
      - The Vice President Takes the Oath of Office
      - The President Takes the Oath of Office
      - Third Term Address
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr026b
      - Third Term Address (continued)
  - SR027, circa 1941-1946, 1 10-inch disc
    Some selections may have been recorded from radio broadcasts.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr027a
      - Talk given by Eloise Hubbard Linscott
    - Side B: Testing, afc1942002_sr027b
      - Opera selections
      - And Love Was Born (from the show "Music in the Air")
  - SR028, circa 1940s, 1 10-inch disc
    Recorded from a radio broadcast on WORL
    - Side A: Singing Advertisements, afc1942002_sr028a
      - Dawson's Ale
      - Six Lil Tailors [Six Little Tailors]
      - Garrett Wine
      - Announcements
      - Kay Jewelers
    - Side B: Singing Advertisements, afc1942002_sr028b
      - Testing
      - Pepsi Cola
      - G. Washington Coffee
      - Announcment
      - Colgate toothpaste
      - Windsor's Furniture
      - Mrs. Filbert's margarine
  - SR029, March 27, 1942, 1 10-inch disc
    Recorded from a bedroom window. Side B is blank.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr029a
      - Song of a robin (and possibly a blue jay)
  - SR030, July 23, 1946 (Side A); July 24-26, 1946, 1 10-inch disc
    Performed by Harry A. Simpson, in Portsmouth, New Hampshire.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr030a
      - Young Albion the Chieftain
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr030b
      - Young Albion the Chieftain
  - SR031, September 1, 1940, 1 10-inch disc
    Performed by Everett Davey (vocals and guitar). Collector's original ID: I (Side A); II (Side B).
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr031a
      - Billy Boy
      - Canaday I-O
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr031b
      - Barbry Ellen [Barbara Allen]
      - Little Mohea [Lass of Mohea]
  - SR032
    - Side A:, October 29, 1943, 1 10-inch disc; afc1942002_sr032a
      Performed by Carrie Grover (vocals), in Gorham, Maine. Collector's original ID: XII.
      - Trooper and the Sailor (Three Cornered Cupboard)
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr032b
      - Donald Monroe
  - SR033, October 29, 1943 (Side A); October 30, 1943 (Side B), 1 10-inch disc
    Performed by Carrie Grover (vocals), in Gorham, Maine. Collector's original ID: XV.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr033a
      - Fair Lady Leroy
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr033b
      - Jack Monroe
      - Erin So Far Away
      - Cork Leg (fragment)
  - SR034, November 12, 1941, 1 10-inch disc
    Performed by Wynifred Staples Smith, in Dixfield, Maine. The audio was recorded at the wrong speed. Side B contains no audible sound recording.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr034a
      - Blow, Boys, Blow (Penobscot River chantey) (fragment)
      - Jean Francois (fragment) [Boney Was A Warrior]
      - Maid of the Mountain Brow (fragment)
      - Sons of Liberty (fragment)
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr034b
      - Untitled
  - SR035, September 27, 1947, 1 10-inch disc
    Performed by William (Bill) Garrity, in Berlin, New Hampshire. Collector's original ID: I.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr035a
      - Plain Golden Band
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr035b
      - Indian's Lament
  - SR036, September 27, 1947, 1 10-inch disc
    Performed by William (Bill) Garrity, in Berlin, New Hampshire. Collector's original ID: III.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr036a
      - The Flying Cloud
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr036b
      - The Flying Cloud (continued)
  - SR037, September 28, 1947, 1 10-inch disc
    Performed by William (Bill) Garrity, in Berlin, New Hampshire. Collector's original ID: IV.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr037a
      - When You Ask a Girl to Leave Her Happy Home
      - The Jam on Gerry's Rocks
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr037b
      - I Can't Tell Why I Love You But I Do
  - SR038, September 27, 1947, 1 10-inch disc
    Performed by William (Bill) Garrity, in Berlin, New Hampshire. Collector's original ID: II.
    - Side A:, afc1942002_sr038a
      - Man Behind the Plough
      - Burning of the Granite Mills (Fall River Fire) (fragment)
    - Side B:, afc1942002_sr038b